payvand.com 2019-09-02

# Payvand.com Privacy Policy

**Payvand.com Privacy Notice**

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for [payvand.com](http://www.payvand.com/) website.  Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. 

For each visitor to our Web page, we collect only the domain name, but not the e-mail address of visitors to our Web page, aggregate information on what pages consumers access or visit, information volunteered by the consumer, such as survey information and/or site registrations, but no information on consumers who browse our Web page.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, , disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets or other corporate change respecting the Website.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**

We are the sole owners of the information that we collect on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you.  You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter through email. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the registration form. We do not set any cookies. Also, we will not sell or rent this information to anyone. 

**Ad Servers**

To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have a relationships with [Google](http://www.google.com/) that we allow to place ads on our Web pages. As a result of your visit to our site, [Google](http://www.google.com/) may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and location information. Please consult the [privacy policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) of [Google](http://www.google.com/) for full disclosure on the information that is collected and to learn how you can adjust your profile setting or opt out of certain [Google](http://www.google.com/) advertising services.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**  

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via [ info@payvand.com](mailto:info@payvand.com). 

  * See what data we have about you, if any.
  * Change/correct any data we have about you.
  * Have us delete any data we have about you.
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Security**  

We take precautions to protect your information.  To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. 

**Updates**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately at [info@payvand.com](mailto:info@payvand.com).
